now let's take the conversation forward
manes manes some would argue that
today's price action in Banks is also a
function of what we heard over heard
from RBI on
Friday yes in a way you right there is
caution in the air as far as the banking
space is concerned but nevertheless one
should mention here that the first
quarter result of most banks have been a
positive surprise simply because of two
things one the moratorium given by the
RBI has not been used to the fullest
extent by the bank customers so that
tells you there is uh a great deal of
cash liquidity available with many of
the clients of the banks that's number
one number two even in this situation of
low GDP growth low um uh growth
environment the banks are able to push
through credit and are able to post
profits thereby upping their net worth
so
I I guess these two points are more
important but yes you are right the
caution by the RBI is in the air and
that's why the bank stocks have
corrected so would you take the RBI
stance seriously because the regulator
rarely comes out and talks about the
liquidity or the balance sheet or the
NPA concerns I mean the regulator does
not like to comment on the problems the
and especially in this kind of an
environment if RBI is raising a red flag
do you think analysts and fund managers
and investors should not take it
lightly they should in incidently to the
extent of what caution has been factored
in in the um the stock prices what is
more important to from the analyst point
of view or the stock markets point of
view so every news as you are aware gets
discounted every uh uh Outlook every
fundamental Outlook gets priced in uh
much before that Outlook actually uh
takes shape so I would reckon that the
stock prices when they correct or they
have been on a steady path right now
would suggest that many of the bank
stocks have already priced in this um
this effect of higher NPS that are
likely to happen or likely to come into
the banking system uh after say October
or
thereabouts m z came out with very poor
set of numbers question marks have been
raised on the kind accounting they
followed I mean nothing's gone wrong in
the covid quarter so much for a media
company that they had to do write off in
subscription right off in advertising
and also other uh you know accounting
write offs but the stock is holding on I
mean with this kind of a number the
stock should have got punchered but it
is down 5 six rupees why is
that it's really surprising actually and
uh much of it is also got to do with the
promoter issues that that it has been
plagued with in the past uh while while
the promoter issues are gradually
getting addressed uh the score
performance of the media company was
never under question in the past it's
been this quarter that we have seen uh Z
really come out
with host of accounting adjustments
which they have not done so before but
even then um uh one may argue that while
the co- performance of a company like Z
Would from a forward-looking perspective
remain unaltered uh one has to really
take a a pause on and and look at
whether the valuations justify what the
core Outlook will be right now I would
say uh the risk reward is right uh
favoring a z given the sharp fall in the
stock uh normally speaking sh a fall in
the stock also enhances the risk reward
ratio so that is what is really
happening right now
okay that's the word coming in on u z
and of course KK is a stock that we are
tracking uh for the market though we're
about a half a percent lower 1120 is
where we're currently at for the Nifty
Futures the breath of course has been
weak from the word go excuse me icsa
bank that's one stock that I just want
to bring up for you on your screens
that's down at the lows of the day it's
a 6% cut that we're seeing on ICC Bank
it was closer to 400 just last week and
after its earnings most of that price
action has gotten undone just about
defending 360 now on the Nifty Futures
Canal a word on IC bank and the kind of
weakness that you're seeing on the stock
after its
earnings yeah I think it's you know
surprised you know most of the guys
because I think post you know the
earnings everyone was expecting that IC
Bank could probably come back to those
390 395 levels which it Ed I think on
Thursday or Wednesday if I'm not wrong
so there was some sort of a positive
expectation in fact even on the data
front it was completely opposite of how
the access bank positioning happened so
remember clearly that we were discussing
that how access bank there were many
shots which were built up for IC Bank it
was completely content there were many
Longs which were built up so you know
the uh the puts of 370 strike 380 strike
as well were the ones which were written
up you know into and generally when you
write uh when Traders write put options
the expectation is that you know the the
stock would not fall below those kind of
levels and there would be some
expectation of a bounce back happening
into those names but again I think you
know the the markets are now trying to
surprise many of the uh you short-term
tra especially on the results front
where there are weaker set of numbers
the stock generally goes through a
bounce back and when there are you know
some stronger set of numbers the stock
generally goes through a corrective
phase so I think in that regards maybe
IC bank is going through a bit of a cont
run or a reversal trade over here I
still believe that 340 360 350 Zone is a
very important support zone for ICA Bank
uh maybe the stock can test that level
over the next you know couple of days
but I think at those levels uh you know
Traders should look at maybe for a
contra buy Behavior because then icsi
Bank as well as the Banky overall could
get back into an extremely oversold
territory which again attracts a very
good risk reward to enter fresh
Longs technology though that's really
one pillar which is holding on in
today's trading session so B
Technologies which is up 3 and a/ qu%
TCS enforces techm they're all names
which are actually holding out uh so se
sectorally you would have to say this is
that one Trend which is actually looking
good add to that cement as well ultr
cement holding out you've got uja as
well which is looking very strong so
both these names are giving you traction
of about 3 to 3 and a half% a piece and
besides that there's agent pains as well
which after its earnings just last week
has managed to really hold strong
another 3 and a half% bump up is what
you're seeing on Asian paints as well
manes any ancillary Trends to you know
the economic activity picking up beat
paines beat cements that you think are
investment
worthy so the discretionary spends is
what is this uh is going to rise up or
there will be an upgrade that will
happen in the way people will start
spending and therefore consumer
discretionary is the space to watch out
for we already know that the rural
economy thanks to buyant agricultural
activi is doing really well and that
that helps up uh Drive demand for
Consumer durables and and hence we would
be looking at the discretionary space So
within the discretionary space consumer
discretionary space the spectrum is
large it starts from something like
automobiles to Home Appliances to even
uh such thing as apparel and clothing uh
now in this respect I would reckon that
the the automobile space particularly
the two- wheeler space will will do
better home appliances will continue to
to uh do well and we will potentially
see pent up demand in such things as
let's say room air conditioners to to TV
sets to to you know host of other
appliances uh that is like come the
festival season uh we will see
discretionary spans going up consumer
dur
therefore would be the ones to watch out
for all right in fact let's listen into
U the management of Asian pains the
numberers still better than what was
expected this time around we actually
spoke to Amit single hear him out
[Music]
okay great uh see uh because of the
lockdown we have been practically closed
from 20th of March to about end of April
so the entire month of April was an
absolute wash out as we see it and we
really opened up only in the month of
May so what we saw in the month of May
was definitely a lot of paint up demand
because the markets were Clos for so
much time and people had to kind of
really look at some of those uh real
pent up maintenance issues which had
come up and therefore I would say that
the month of May largely went in terms
of really satisfying the pent up demand
across uh the country uh however I think
the good part was that uh in the month
of June uh triggered by our safe
painting Campaign which really uh kind
of gave the people confidence that you
can get a set of painters into your
house and it is safe to kind of do and
get into painting we saw a lot of
secondary demand uh come up across the
cities and that has uh boosted our
confidence that it was not only the pent
of demand which was kind of there in May
but a lot of new demand which came in
both in the area of painting
waterproofing and so on so forth LED
also by another campaign which we did
which was Terrace waterproofing so we
feel that a lot of demand which has come
in in the month of June is definitely
new PIN demand which is kind of boosting
our confidence in terms of you know how
possibly we are looking looking at the
market at the
moment okay so that's on Asian paints uh
let's just take a look at uh what else
is uh in Focus uh this afternoon I mean
we touched upon some of the move that
we're seeing on a couple of those
earnings reactions as well as it names
but overall the trend is definitely
weaker today uh mahantesh let's get your
take on some of the it names then it's
not just the front lers but also the
midcap names that have definitely been
standing out of late uh you know what
would you what kind of uh you know
preference or weightage would you really
give some of these it counters at this
point of
time uh if you recall when the covid
phenomenon began in March we were the
ones who were saying that it company or
it sector as a whole will continue to do
well uh and the uh that particular
prediction is somehow coming true and
that's simply because it companies are
first you know first first and foremost
they accustomed to the work work at work
from home kind of environment number two
uh there is an unabated kind of activity
happening on the deal side many of the
it companies constantly work towards
engaging more and more clients uh both
horizontally as well as vertically and
therefore large deal winds are coming uh
to to to the kitty of most most of the
it companies that's is what is driving
up many of the it companies apart from
the defensive strategies that most uh
people would have applied applied by by
pushing their portfolio into the IT
stock so right now I would say that the
outlook for it companies is
strengthening because there is a lot of
background work on Deal activity that
has happened and which will come to the
surface once uh uh once we get more in
in forther into the fiscal year and most
of the it companies have also
demonstrated that they are able to up
their margins in this period in this
period of lockdown so healthy set of
financial numbers are getting posted I
wouldn't be surprised if it companies
further get rated
upwards all right in conversation with
San and we've got manes sabat but the
stock which I want to flag off is
actually MCX and Stock Exchange uh
exchanges are today on a
tear exchanges are essentially like
modern platforms app Point what herin
was making and some of these exchanges
surely have a long way to go given that
the trading volumes globally by Robin
Hood Traders and in India by work atome
Traders has actually uh just
intensified manes you
know I I refuse to buy the argument when
everybody's saying that just because
retail investors are back or retail
Traders are there and volumes are going
higher it's time to really blow the
trumpet and it's time to get out you
know sometimes I wonder that why do you
always look down at retail investors and
when retail investors or retail Traders
are always buying that is sign of a
market Peak I mean retail guys bought
gold couple of years ago gold has given
great returns they avoided Equity couple
of years ago and Equity has not given
great returns in 3 4 years
so uh what is the question uh uh
nikun my question mes is that every
large Institutional Investor who comes
on our Channel and various
forums is always flagging off the fact
that you know retail investors are there
you should avoid the market there is
momentum and there is this for more
effect which has kicked in would you buy
this argument historically we've always
used the retail activity as a benchmark
of what not to do rather what to do now
the retail activity is back what should
one how should one read into it so uh uh
you know in a way the the Market's
perception about retail investors
actually entering in the market and
taking it higher to a level where it's
right time to sell has been simply
because retail investors have largely
been interested in small cap names and
midcap names in the equities uh but that
is not the case when the current
environment where you have these Robin
Hood investors the Robin Hood investors
are taking equal interest in even large
cap names uh and and investing in in the
broader set of uh stocks and and
therefore this effect or this perception
about retail investors being taking the
market to a level which is unsustainably
high it doesn't hold through any longer
at least in this environment they are
not into large cap midcap stocks it's
sorry they're not into small cap midcap
stocks they're into the large cap stocks
and therefore I I would Recon that today
most of these retail investors are
becoming a lot more savier they have a l
a large amount of uh research advice
backing them up uh that research advice
is coming in through through a lot of
platform kind of guys that you just
talked about and so research is
available tailor made available at your
fingertips and and good quality research
is available even to the retail
investors no longer it is the case that
institutional investors would have
quality research behind them backing
their ideas backing their stock buys
retail investors also have quality
advice and I would reckon that this
phenomenon of the market going up with
higher retail participation
will will continue for for some more
time because they have they are also
getting invested into the large cap
names so yes to some extent I agree with
what you are trying to say that it's
it's the back picture that gets painted
when retail investors enter the market
is no longer true